# Sara Ortega Zúñiga



605 574 597



Recently graduated in Web Development. Two years of academy and the dedication to personal projects have allowed me to gain experience in solving complex problems using different technologies and frameworks.

The programming passion has led me to completely rethink my professional career. I am excited to join a dynamic and collaborative team where I can contribute my skills and knowledge.



#### **Education** Skills

# **Computer Science: Web Development Higher National Diploma**

Institut Obert de Catalunya (IOC) 2021-2023

Backend, Frontend, Relational Databases, **Systems** 

# Administration and Finance Higher **National Diploma**

IES Severo Ochoa 2010-2012

**Experience** 

### Parking Manager in El Nou Raval SL

2016 to date

In charge of collection, products and daily issues. Managins a team of 5.

# Administrative clerk in Galdón-Rodríguez **Notary**

2013-2015

Responsible for the maintenance and update of the Databases of the notary.

Preparation of notarial documentation

# **Coordinator in Emergency Service 112**

2009-2013

Activation and coordination of emergency services (firefighters, police, ambulance...).

- HTML / CSS / JavaScript / ES6
- Bootstrap / JQuery / Ajax
- XML / JSON
- React.js
- Java 11 / JavaEE / Java-Spring
- SpringBoot / MVC
- SQL / MySQL
- Apache / WAMP
- Git / Github / Taiga Scrum Kanban
- Netbeans / Eclipse / Visual Studio Code

# Soft-skills

- Problem-solving
- **Decision-making**
- Critical and logical thinking
- Organisational and time management
- Open-mindedness and adaptability
- Teamwork and collaboration
- Empathy and patience

# Languages

- English Intermediate B1
- **Spanish** Native
- Catalan Native
- Italian Basic